cnccookbook.com 2015-06-27

# CNC Cookbook : Privacy Policy

CNCCookbook's Privacy Policy

At CNCCookbook, we are committed to having fanatically loyal customers. Part of that is making sure that we treat your privacy with respect.

This Privacy Policy describes how we collect personal information from our users and how that information is used and disclosed by CNCCookbook. The Policy applies solely to information we collect from this website and our CNCCookbook software. It will notify you of the following: 

  * What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared. 
  * What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data. 
  * The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information. 
  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. 

**Our privacy policy was originally created by TRUSTe.**

## Collection and Use of Personal Information

We collect the following personal information from you

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number
  * Unique Identifiers such as user name, account number, password
  * Preferences Information such as product wish lists, order history, marketing preferences

As is true of most Web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system.

We use this information to

  * Fulfill your order
  * Send you an order confirmation
  * Assess the needs of your business to determine suitable products
  * Send you requested product or service information
  * Send product updates or warranty information
  * Respond to customer service requests
  * Administer your account
  * Send you a newsletter
  * Send you marketing communications
  * Administer contests and sweepstakes you entered, and notify you if you won
  * Respond to your questions and concerns
  * Improve our Web site and marketing efforts
  * Improve our software
  * Conduct research and analysis
  * Display content based upon your interests

**Choice/Opt-Out**

You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you can contact us at [sales@cnccookbook.com ](mailto:sales@cnccookbook.com).

**Information Obtained from Third Parties**

If you provide us personal information about others, or if others give us your information, we will only use that information for the specific reason for which it was provided to us.

## Information Sharing

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information  _only as necessary to provide_  these services to us.

We may also disclose your personal information

  * as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,
  * if CNCCookbook is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information,
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

_PayPal_

If you choose to use PayPal to finalize and pay for your order, you will provide your credit card number, directly to PayPal. PayPal's privacy policy will apply to the information you provide on the PayPal Web site.

## Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

We may use cookies, for example, to keep track of your preferences and profile information. Cookies are also used to collect general usage and volume statistical information that does not include personal information.

We use another company to place cookies on your computer to collect non-personally identifiable information to compile aggregated statistics for us about visitors to our site.

_Web beacons_

Our Web pages contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) and are used along with cookies to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used and may be used in some of our emails to let us know which emails and links have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of our customer communications and marketing campaigns.

Our Web pages may also contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) that are set by our third party partners. Web beacons are used along with cookies enabling our partners to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used.

We use a third party to gather information about how you and others use our Web site. For example, we will know how many users access a specific page and which links they clicked on. We use this aggregated information to understand and optimize how our site is used.

_Links to Other Web Sites_

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of CNCCookbook. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit.

## Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at [sales@cnccookbook.com](mailto:sales@cnccookbook.com)

We provide two means for you to make a purchase on our site. You can either use our order form or a third party payment option. If you use our shopping cart, the transmission of sensitive information collected on our order form is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL). If you choose to use a third party payment option to pay for your order, its privacy statement and security practices will apply to your information. We encourage you to read that privacy statement before providing your information.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at [sales@cnccookbook.com](mailto:sales@cnccookbook.com). We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

## Additional Policy Information

Our Web site includes Widgets, which are interactive mini-programs that run on our site to provide specific services from another company (e.g. displaying the news, opinions, music, etc). Personal information, such as your email address, may be collected through the Widget. Cookies may also be set by the Widget to enable it to function properly. Information collected by this Widget is governed by the privacy policy of the company that created it.

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them.

**Correcting and Updating Your Personal Information**

To review and update your personal information to ensure it is accurate, contact us at [sales@cnccookbook.com ](mailto:sales@cnccookbook.com).

**Notification of Privacy Statement Changes**

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

You can contact us about this privacy statement by writing or email us at the address below:

CNCCookbook

3470 Merrill Rd

Aptos, CA, United States 95003

Phone: 4084253617
